Inventory of the Overseas Weekly photographs
Hoover Institution Archives
- Contact Sheet 14915, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - Sp4 James Crawford & victim's family.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID Sheet for Crawford Murder Trial - Jan. 26 - Frames 5a, 6a: 5p4 James Crawford. Frames 9-11: The daughter Nguyen Thi Ma. Frames 12-14: the father, Nguyen Van Vu.
- Contact Sheet 14916, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - AWOL - Pfc. Larry K. Patton - Capt. Edwin S. Zeitlin.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: overs pazifik - Jan. 26 - Patton negatives - Patton is tallest man in photo, fourth from left and walking toward camera. Red arrow points to him. At far right is his lawyer, Capt Edwin S. Zeitlin. Frame 3: Patton walks in door (his back to camera); Zeitlin follows him. Man at right.
- Contact Sheet 14917, 1969 February 15
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - leave towns (Koza / Okinawa).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Foto ids - Koza city night life - strip one - Frame 11: Gate Two Street (taken in the daytime). Frame 12: A sign advertising the strip show inside one of the koza city bars. Frame 13: Koza city street scene with some of the cute little japanese chicks crossing the street. 14: One of the off-duty bargirls waiting to be picked up (This was shot in daylight and girl probably isn't really a bargirl, but her stance is typical.). - Strip two - Frame 7: disregard -- local nice girl with her boyfriend. Frame 8, 9, & 10: Gate Two Street in daytime showing boocoo bars. - Strip three - Frames 8, 9, & 10: Three shots of Gate Two Street taken at night showing the lights of town, boocoo bars all lit up.
- Contact Sheet 14919, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - music groups (mil band).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: overs pazifik - jan. 18 - ID for contact shee B -- All are pictures of American Division musicians, part of the division band, who go to the Chu Lai Air Base passenger terminal every day at noon to play for the scores of Marines and GIs waiting for R&R flights and freedom flights home. The director is Sp5 Phil Heldon; the bass horn player in Frames 3-7 is Sp4 William Dew; the trombone player, frames 1-2, is Sp5 George Pempsell.
- Contact Sheet 14920, 1969 February 22
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - medical corps - Att revival of Ptc. Rodney W. Pavao - Feb. / 22 / '69 / Pac.
- Contact Sheet 14921, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces camps - strip one.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Foto id -- sheet I - Feb. 3 - Frame 2: American special forces team boards Caribou to leave Gia Vuc valley. 3: 4: Montagnard kids stand in front of school house at "Gia Vuc Hamlet C" near the special forces camp. The school house was built with encouragement of American SF team, but Montagnard tribesmen did all the work. Permission of the spirits had to be obtained before classes could be started at the school. Spirits at Gia Vuc were favorable and classes are held every day. 5: Montagnard boy from Hre tribe stands leaning on edge of family porch of village chief's house. He is son of chief, who has five wives. A Montagnard house has two porches, one on either end of house. One porch is restricted to family use and other is for visitors to house. 6: Hre woman with her baby stands in front of visitor's porch to her house. Visitors do not enter house until invited by head of household. When visitors do enter, protocol calls for sips of rice wine from a huge vase. Rice wine is sipped through a rice stalk which is passed from right to left. It is considered to be an insult if you hand the montagnard a sip of rice win with your left hand -- The right hand is good, and the left hand is bad. 7: 12-year-old montagnard girl holds her baby (bundle in her arms). By the time she's old enough to be married (about 14) she'll have a good start on a family. 8: Old montagnard woman from Hre tribe sits on family porch of her house. 9, 10: Montagnard woman and her brood poses for OW's fotog on family porch. 11, 12: Montagnard cemetary. Houses are erected over graves to shelter the spirits of the dead. Whenever a montagnard dies his share of the family's wealth is buried in the grave with him (if there are eight people in the family 1/8 of the family's wealth is buried with him). 13: Fields of IR-8 "mirien rice" with montagnard villagers working the rice plots. Montagnard villages are a form of communism, with all property belonging to village as a whole and none to an individual. Plots are allotted to families according to their rank and family wealth. The richest and most important man gets the most land, and the land is usually that closest to his house so that he doesn't have to go so far to work it. The poorer a man is, the farther he has to walk to his fields and the fewer fields he has. 14: A herd of Montagnard ducks in foreground, a mama-san and her son taking a bath in the middle of a tribal cemetary in the background. 15: A herd of ducks. 16: ??? 17, 18: Vietnamese and montagnard children attend the schools in hamlet A, the only village in Vietnam were Vietnamese and Montagnards live and work side-by-side and send their kids to the same schools. This village has two schools, one for grades one thru three and one for grades four thru six. Spirit's permission had to be granted for opening of school, which was built by villagers with encouragement of American Special Forces.
- Contact Sheet 14922, 1969 February 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces camps - strip two.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Foto id's -- sheet two - Feb. 3 - Frame 2a: two montagnard boys at Gia Vuc tend their herd of water buffalo. Water buffalo are one measure of a family's wealth 3a: ???? 10a: Aerial photo of Gia Vuc Hamlet C. A typical Montagnard village. 12a: Montagnard villagers walk along airstrip at Gia Vuc Special Forces Camp. 13a: Special Forces brass comes from Nha Trang to take part in turning over of command ceremony (Colonel Aaron, 5th SF GP CO was conspicuous by his absence). 14a: U.S. and Vietnamese Special Forces brass review Montagnard Civilian Irregular Defense Group troops at Gia Vuc SF camp. 15a thru 20a: The Vietnamese flag is raised alone for the first time over Gia Vuc SF Camp (Before, the U.S. Flag was hoisted alongsite the Vietnamese Flag). Extra photo: Montagnard CIDG troopers stand at parade rest during change of command ceremonies.
- Contact Sheet 14923, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces camps - strip three.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo ids -- sheet three - Feb. 3 - Frame 2: Vietnamese Special Forces trooper is congratulated by US SF brass from 5th SF Gp Hq in turning over of command ceremony. 3: Vietnamese Special Forces Group CO and staff reviews troops during ceremony. 4: CIDG Honor Guard salutes as brass leaves compound. 5, 6, 7: Vietnamese SF paratroopers suit up for demonstration jump to impress Hre villagers at conclusion of ceremony. 8: Smoke is popped to show wind direction for descending Viet paratroopers during jump demonstration. 9 thru 18: Viet paratroopers -- leaving chopper and landing and floating down, etc. 19: A little bit of civic action. US SF S Sgt Edward G. Salaz hands out candy to Vietnamese and Montagnard kids as his last civic action project before pulling out of Gia Vuc Valley for good. 20, 21: Capt. Edwin C. Sittler, US Camp advisor CO and Camp Commander Nguyen Tai Chu exchange gifts as a sign of lasting friendship during handing over of camp to Chu and his team.
- Contact Sheet 14924, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces camps-strip four.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo id -- sheet four - Feb. 03 - Frame 2: Two cute young things from the Vietnamese Political Warfare Team, visiting Gia Vie to put on skits and entertainment for the Vietnamese and CIDG troopers are pressed into service to take part in the ceremony. They hand the gifts in their hands to Sittler and Chu, who then exchange gifts as a sign of everlasting friendship. 3: Cu makes his acceptance speech at rostrum as Sittler (right -- the tall guy) looks on. 4: The PoliWar girls relax at rear of reviewing stand and get instructions from the ceremony's coordinating officer. 5: The American team, with packs and rifles ready for leaving stand facing their CIDG troopers across the camp square. 6: Troops gathered in camp square for ceremony. 7: The Vietnamese SF team stands at attention as their CO accepts the camp. 8: The reviewing stand. 9: The assembled Hre Village, Hamlet and Tribal chiefs watch the ceremony as Captain Chu speaks at rostrum. 10: View of the camp. 11: Hre chiefs watch ceremony. 12: ???? 13: American team with packs and weaponds, ready to go home. 14, 15: Hre chiefs watch ceremony. 16: Capt Chu (short guy, left) and Capt Sittler (right) salute reviewing stand at conclusion of change of command. 17: Somebody making another tiresome speech. 18: 19: Vietnamese special Forces Group CO makes his spiel. 20: Vietnamese SF troopers give gift to Sittler (tall guy in middle) as the two PoliWar girls depart the area. 21: Viet SF team (Sittler hidden behind them).
- Contact Sheet 14925, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - shows - Marines.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Caption Notes for 3rd Marine Div Pix - Jan 26 - Dan Derby - c/c JUSPAO Press Mission - APO San Francisco, 96243 - entertainment photos - the Vegas Variety is but one of the many groups now playing the 3rd Div. circuit. Shows like the one shown at Cua Viet, only 10 kilometers south of the DMZ, are possible due to the efforts of Commanding General Raymond G. Davis. Davis has turned Cua Viet into a unit R&R area where filed troops can get a two or three day break from the war to sun, swim and watch a show or two.
- Contact Sheet 14926, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam show - marines.
- Contact Sheet 14927, 1969 February 22
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - rescue missions - Cwo. Patrick Gwaltney - Wo. Bob Satterfield.
- Contact Sheet 14929, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - long range patrols -Maj. Joe Schmek - printed March 1, '69.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Contact Sheet A - 12 shots lurps for close call story (l-r) Pfc Mikulenka, Sp4 Honeyman, Sp4 Schaad talk over their close call. 12 shots of Kit Carson Scout Tran Van Wang. GI, Pfc Charles Laney. 8 shots of Maj Joe Shmek playing a tune on his bagpipes.
- Contact Sheet 14931, 1969 January 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - press - Maj. Jimmy E. Wilson.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Jan. 4 - Contact sheet H - Both photos show Maj Jimmy E. Wilson, editor of new bilingual newspaper, talking with a printing plant official in Saigon, where paper is printed. OW Photo by Forken.
- Contact Sheet 14933, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - religion - Chapl (Maj.) - James M. Kennedy.
- Contact Sheet 14935, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - show - Carl. Perkins - " B " - Johnny Cash.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet B -- Jonny Cash - frame 2a the band. 3a-14a: Carl Perkins and guitar. Rest of roll -- GI reactions to show at main Em Club on Long Binh Post.
- Contact Sheet 14936, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - show - "C" - Johnny Cash - June Carter.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet C - Johnny Cash - 3a-16a: June Carter (Mrs. Johnny Cash). 17a, 18a: GI reaction. 19a, 20a: Johnny Cash is mobbed by eager GI's when he comes onstage rest of roll -- Johnny Cash playing guitar.
- Contact Sheet 14937, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - show - "D" - Johnny Cash.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet D -- Johnny Cash - Frames 3-13: More shots of Johnny Cash singing etc. 14-16: Cash loosens jacket, takes it off, and then accepts written requests for songs from GIs. 17: More audience reaction.
- Contact Sheet 14938, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - show - "E" - Jonny Cash - Carl Perkins.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheet for Man on Street and Johnny Cash - Frames 3a, 4a: Ditto (L-R), Perkins, Cash and Carter. Rest of Roll: (L-R) Carter, Cash, Perkins sign autographs and shake hands with Gis at close of show.
- Contact Sheet 14939, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - prisons (Oki Stockade) - Sparky J. Rose (accused) - Capt. Lawrence Sandell (prosecutor).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Foto IDs -- Stockade trials - Frame 2: Capt. Lawrence Sandell, prosecutor for the series of trials. He won every case. 3 thru 6: Prisoner Sparky J. Rose stands outside courtroom door with guards from JS.
- Contact Sheet 14940, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - clubs (fancy off. clubs).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Feb. 1 - Dan Derby - JUSPAO Press Mission - APO San Francisco 96243 - Photos of the The Club Car (BOQ 1) - Background: The officer's club for BOQ 1 has been remodeled in the form of an oversized railroad car. Floors have wall-to-wall carpeting, walls are stained wood. Tables and chairs are also dark stained wood, in mock early American style. Where windows would be in a railroad club car there are lighted transparencies of scenes like Mount Vernon. All along the right wall (as you face the stage) is a continuous upholstered bench. The stage is a small raised platform in dark wood, with a movie screen behind it. When the screen is not in use a silent-film still picture is mounted on it. Caption: the brass at BOQ 1 has created for themselves one of the most luxurious clubs in Vietnam, the Club Car. Modeled after a railway car the club stands on the second floor of the officers mess -- HIGH class. "You get to this place and you forget where you're at," said one Lite Colonel. Junior officers are welcome to go there to drink and forget, too.
- Contact Sheet 14942, 1969 March 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - shooting - Seaman Charles Tutt - Lt. David H. Barry (Def.) - Lt. James Fitzgerald (prosecutor).
- Contact Sheet 14943, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - SF Vietnam hospital roll 1 - Special forces Dr. (Capt.) Eugene McDannald.
- Contact Sheet 14944, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - SF hospital roll 2 - Vietnam hospital - special forces.
- Contact Sheet 14945, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - SF hospital roll 3 - Vietnam hospital - special forces - Sp4 Donald Carpenter.
- Contact Sheet 14946, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - SF Vietnames Hospital roll 4 - special forces.
- Contact Sheet 14947, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - SF Vietnam Hospital roll 5 - Special Forces.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo ID - SF hospital - Reynolds - 2a: The chief cook and bottle washer at the hospital. 4a, 5a, 6a, 7a, 8a: Vietnamese medics work over a patient scrubbing down a skin graft on his leg. 9a: Doc McDannald checks over hand on patient before doing skin-graft. This guy had little finger on right hand amputated. Doc is going to do skin graft on stub of finger. 10a: same 9a. 11a: Doc MacDannald and Sp4 McWorter do skin graft on patient's hand with help from VN medic.
- Contact Sheet 14948, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - prison Cu Chi Blast - inside prison MP check at gate - sheet D.
- Contact Sheet 14949, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - prison - Pvt. George Ognag - Sgt. Robert Adams - AWOL trial - Cu-chi blast - sheet "E" - Pfc. Wendell Leslie.
- Contact Sheet 14950, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - casualty - 1st Lt. Richard Askins - Dr.(Capt.) Prentiss Smith - hospital - Feb./ 1 / '69, only story.
- Contact Sheet 14952, 1969 February 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - roll G - civic action - Cpl. James E. Zajic - Cpl. Harold Watt - story printed Feb./ 8 / '69.
- Contact Sheet 14953, 1969 February 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - roll H - Vietnam civic action - Cpl. John Enge Bretsen.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Foto ID - roll H - for civic action platoon story - frames 3-6: Shots of scenery between Da Nang and district headquarters at Hieu Due. 7: ID sign at Hieu Duc. 8: District police headquarters at Hieu Due. 9: District admin office at Hieu Due. 10, 11: More scenery between Hieu Due and one of the CAPs at La Chau (Cpl Engebretson's post). 12, 13: Aerial shot of CAP compound at La Chau. 14: Cpl John Engebretson, honcho of La Chau CAP. 15: Defense trench around La Chau CAP compound. 16: Admin shack at La Chau. 17: GI's rest along road after making sweep of area. 18: Tuy Loan village main street. 19, 20: Marine holds live (dud) 81mm mortar round brought in by Vietnamese villager who got 400 piaster reward for it. 21: Villager gets 400 pee payoff for 81 mm mortar round. 22, 23: Shot of La Chau CAP compund. 24-36: Shots of La Chau village (26: A CAP marine and VN popular forces buddy walk down main street of village).
- Contact Sheet 14954, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - shooting - Pvt. John O'Sullivan.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Foto ID - O'sullivan trial - 11 Jan '68 - 5: O'Sullivan, defense witness Steven P. Jett and Howard sit in waiting room during trial. 6: O'Sullivan and Jett. O'Sullivan reading a copy of OW. 7: O'Sullivan, Jett and Howard. 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14: O'Sullivan and Jett. 15: O'Sullivan, Jett and Howard. 16: O'Sullivan and Jett. 17, 18: Murder witness Nguyen Thi Ngoc Nghia, bargirl at San Francisco bar, leaves courtroom after testifying against O'Sullivan. With her is prosecutor Capt. William C. Lanham. 19: Nguyen Thi Ngoc Nghia leaves courtroom after testifying. 21, 22: Lam Thi Ngoc Lan talks with GI guards in hallway outside courtroom while waiting to testify. 23: Miss Lam shies away from camera while GI guard tries to talk her into posing for OW fotog. 26: Lam complains to Prosecuter… her wishes. Sorry 'bout that.
- Contact Sheet 14975, 1969 March 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - shooting - Sgt. Dwayne A. DeVega.
- Contact Sheet 14989, 1968 November 30
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pvt. Robert M. Smith - riots - prisoners - Capt. Donald H. Segretti (defense).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo ID -- Smith trial - Smith right and Defense counsel Segretti talk over file while court considers verdict.
- Contact Sheet 14992, 1968 January 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pfc. Scotty Frazier- assault - drinking.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Frazier trial - photo id - Reynolds - 11 jan 68 - frame 5: Scotty Frazier leaves courtroom. GI guard waits in foreground to snap handcuffs on him. 6, 7, 8, 9, 10: GI guard snaps the cuffs on Fraziers wrists. 11: Frazier, with cuffs on.
- Contact Sheet 14993, 1969 February 15
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - AWOL - assault - Pvt. Sena Benefield - Capt. Robert Raulerson (def.).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheet for awol assault trial - frames 3-5: Benefield (r) and his lawyer Capt. Robert Raulerson talk it over during a break in the trial. Benefield is Negro.
- Contact Sheet 14994, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - leave towns - foreign troops (Australians) - Boonies to beach.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID Sheet for boonies to beach story - Sheet C - Frames 3-14: Shots of helicopters removing guns from Flinders. 15, 16: Aussies talk to helicopters overhead. 16-23: Shots of choppers landing, choppers picking up more gear. 24: Sgt Rich Hampson and Gunner Bob Dennis wait for helicopter. 25: Bdr. Rick Polley cracks a quick laugh. 26-33: Aussies take a break before being lifted out. Note blokes reading OW. 34, 35: Helicopter with slingload. 36, 36A: Group of Aussies waiting to be lifted out.
- Contact Sheet 14995, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - leave towns - foreign troops (Australians) - boonies to beach.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet D - frame 2: John Knight (L) and Dave Thomas (R) remove wire. 4-8: More shots of Aussies removing wire. 9-18: Aussies wait for choppers, load on board. 19-27: Aussies aboard chopper on way back to civilization, walking back from chopper - civilization. 28, 29: Cleaning 105 mm gun.
- Contact Sheet 14996, 1969 February 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - leave towns - Boonies to beach - for troops (Australians).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet E - Frames 3-7: Gunner Phil Smith drinks his first beer in 2 months. 8, 9: Aussies relaxing at party. 10-27: Aussies in formation before move to Vung Tau, trip to Vung Tau countryside. 28, 29: Swimming pool at Peter Badcoe Club. 30-35: Aussies relax at Peter Badcoe Club. 36, 36A: Bdr Vladimir Prock, Gnr Tony Skinner, Gnr John Smith in pool.
- Contact Sheet 14997, 1969 February 1
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet F - Frames 4-10: Shots of Aussies in pool at Peter Badcoe Club. 11, 12: Dino Infaletta takes picture of sleeping beauty Jackie Reiland. 13, 14: More pix of water sports. 15: Aussie upends beer. 16, 17: LBdr Kevin Scrimshaw combs his moustache. 18-28: Aussies eat a decent meal in downtown Vung Tau.
- Contact Sheet 14998, 1969 February 1
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ID sheets for boonies to beach story - Sheet C - Frame 2: Aussies walk street in downtown Vung Tau. 3-6: Kevin Scrimshaw & bar girl. 7: 2/Lt Don Turnbull & bar girl. 8: Gunner Terry & bar girl. 9: W reporter & bar girl.
- Contact Sheet 14999, 1969 March 15
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Philippines - leave towns.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Captions for Manila night life -- other art - Roll #1 - Frames 4a, 51: outside of strip show - the show is lonely. 26a, 24a: Manila harbor at sunset, plus various camera hogs who kept getting in the way. Rest of way roll -- outside Jai Alai.
- Contact Sheet 15000, 1969 March 22
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp4 Mike Fleming (point man) - Sp5 Mckinley Edwards - Pinups (Col. Archie Hyle's hen house) - sheet #1.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Captions for Sheets 1-3 & 5-11 - Sheet 1: frames 2a-6a: Sp4 Fleming - Point Man Story. 7a-9a: 1st Inf. Div. GI - note tasteful pinup on wall on right. 10a, 11a: Sp5 Mckinley Edwards, quote for pinup hen story. Rest of roll: Shots of Hyle's hen house - chickens flew the coop when I approached, so no pix.
- Contact Sheet 15001, 1969 March 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action (near Thu Do) -patrol - sheet 2.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet 2 - Various shots of GiIs in 1st Inf. Div. operation near Thu Due - no names.
- Contact Sheet 15002, 1969 March 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action (flame throwers) - patrol - sheet 3.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet 3 -- flame throwing APC - frames 3a, 4a: Starting to light up. Frames 5a-28a: APC shooting flamethrower -- nicknamed Zippo, and flames and smoke that result. The range is so long that it was almost impossible to get pic of smoke and APC in same frame. Rest of roll -- more pix of same APC after it's stopped shooting fire.
- Contact Sheet 15003, 1969 March 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action - patrol - sheet 4.
- Contact Sheet 15004, 1969 March 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action APGs moving through jungle - patrol.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet 5 -- entire roll shots of APCs moving through jungle.
- Contact Sheet 15005, 1969 March 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action APCs moving - patrol - sheet 6.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet 6 -- Sames as Sheet 5 -- APC patrol.
- Contact Sheet 15006, 1969 March 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action - patrol - sheet 7.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet 7 - frames 9a, 10a: Aviator's helmet with peace symbol on it. 11a-13a: Old French armored car. 14a-19a: More APCs moving through jungle. 20a, 21a: Guy framing APC is Sp4 Salvatore Fernandez. 22a, 27a: More shots moving through jungle. 28a: APC crew take break. 29a: Sp4 Robert Emort, Jr.-- driver. 30a: 1 more shot of crew. 31a-34a: guys try to untangle barbed wire from treads. 35a: ?????
- Contact Sheet 15007, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action - patrol - sheet 8.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet B - frames 2-9: Shots of various APCs and GIs - nothing in particular. 10-12: Sp4 Mike Flemming - Pointman. 13, 14: Nudie photo on wall. Rest of roll 1st Inf. Div. GIs operation near Thu Duc.
- Contact Sheet 15009, 1969 March 22
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action - patrol - sheet 10.